我想爸爸想让我们继续他的工作
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off:
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
Saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
Family business.
晚安 亲爱的
Goodnight, love.
嘿 迪恩
Hey, Dean.
- 爸爸 - 嘿 小伙计
- Daddy. - Hey, buddy.
萨米
Sammy.
玛丽
Mary.
迪恩 这是我的女朋友杰西卡
Dean.This is my girlfriend, Jessica.
为萨姆法学考试胜利干杯
So here's to Sam and his awesome LSAT victory.
- 没有你我该怎么做 - 会死得很惨
- What would I do without you? - Crash and burn.
不
No!
- 我不就这样放弃工作的 - 去他妈的工作 老兄
- I'm not gonna ditch the job. - Screw the job.man
我对工作没有好感 既没人付钱给我们
I'm sick of the job anyway. We don't get paid.
也没人感谢我们 我们得到的只有坏运气
We don't get thanked. The only thing we get's bad luck.
- 是的 - 外面有辆警车
- Yeah? - There's a cop car outside.
- 你认为是给我们的 - 我不知道
- You think it's for us? - I don't know.
我们没留下任何线索
I don't see how. We ditched the plates, the credit cards.
他们走了 是假警报
They're leaving. False alarm.
- 看见了 没什么好担心的 - 做个逃犯
See, nothing to worry about. - Yeah, being fugitives...
- 可不好玩 - 嘿 老兄
- ...is a frigging dance party. - Hey, man...
放松点
chicks dig the danger vibe.
有什么消息吗？开玩笑 我怎么会有？
You got anything? Are you kidding? How could I?
你让我搜查方圆50英里的住宅区
You got me sifting through, like, 50 square miles.
- 所有的被害者都失踪了 - 我在处处蹲点
- That's where the victims disappeared. - I got diddlysquat.
- 你呢？- 只有一件事我现在清楚了
- What about you? - Just one thing. I'm pretty sure of it now.
- 我们在猎杀一个魔鬼 - 一个魔鬼？
- We're hunting a jinn. - A frigging genie?
- 你认为那些混蛋真的能实现你的愿望？- 不知道
- You think these suckers can grant wishes? - I don't know.
我猜它们有足够强大 但不像芭芭拉·艾登的女眷境地一样
They're powerful enough. But not exactly like Barbara Eden in harem pants.
妖魔残害人类已经几个世纪了
Jinn have been feeding off people for centuries.
- 而且都掩盖了"古兰经" - 我的天啊
- They're all over the Koran. - My God.
芭芭拉·艾登很性感不是吗？
Barbara Eden was hot, wasn't she?
甚至比那个着了魔的女人还性感
Way hotter than that Bewitched chick.
你到底有没有在听我说？
Are you even listening to me?
当然 那个妖魔在哪里？
Ahem. Yeah. So where do the jinns lair up?
废弃建筑物里 越大越好 它们都躲在那里
Ruins, usually. The bigger, the better. More places to hide.
几英里那儿有个地方 我回去瞧瞧
I saw a place a few miles back. I'm gonna go check it out.
不… 先来接我
No...Come pick me up first.
我确定那里没什么东西 我只是去看看
No. I'm sure it's nothing. I just wanna take a look around.
[邪恶力量 第2季第20集]
- 迪恩？- 萨姆
- Dean? - Sam.
- 怎么了？- 我不知道 我不知道我在哪儿
What's going on? - I don't know.I don't know where I am.
什么？ 发生什么事了？
What? What happened?
- 那个魔鬼攻击了我 - 松子？
- Well, the jinn, it attacked me. - The gin?
- 你喝了松子酒？- 不是 是魔鬼
- You're drinking gin? - No, ass hat, the jinn.
那可怕的生物 不记得了？
The scary creature, remember?
它把手放在我头上 然后我在一个性感女士的身旁醒来
It put its hand on me and then I woke up next to some hot chick.
谁？ 卡门？
Who, Carmen?
- 谁？- 迪恩 你喝醉了
- Who? - Dean, you're drunk.
- 你喝醉了打了我的电话 - 我没喝醉
- You're drunk-dialing. - I'm not.
- 你别闹了 - 已经很晚了
- Quit screwing around. - It's late.
好了 去睡会儿
All right, just get some sleep.
- 我们明天见 好吗？- 等等 萨姆 萨姆
- I'll see you tomorrow, okay? - Wait, Sam. Sam.
劳伦斯？
Lawrence?
见鬼了？
What the hell?
亲爱的？
Honey?
你在干什么？
What are you doing up?
卡门
Carmen.
卡门 我只是…
Carmen, uh, I just, uh
- 你睡不着是吗？- 是啊
- Oh, you can't sleep, huh? - Yeah. Ha-ha.
那么 不如你先回到床上 我看看能帮上你什么忙吧
Well, why don't you come back to bed and let's see if I can do anything to help?
当然
Sure.
- 先等一下 你先去吧 - 好吧
- Yeah, in a minute. You go ahead. - Okay.
- 别呆太久了 - 不会的
- Don't stay up too long. - No.
迪恩？
Dean.
妈妈？
Mom?
你在这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
- 我不知道 - 那进来吧
- I don't know. - Well, come inside.
卡门打电话来 说你匆忙离开了
Carmen just called and said you just took off all of a sudden.
卡门？
Carmen?
对啊
Right.
问你个问题
Let me ask you a question.
当我还是孩子的时候 每次睡觉时你都和我说了那句话？
When I was a kid, what did you always tell me when you put me to bed?
- 我不明白… - 回答我的问题
- Dean, I don't understand... - Just answer the question.
我告诉你天使一直在照看你
I told you angels were watching over you.
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
亲爱的你吓着我了
Honey, you're scaring me.
- 告诉我到底发生了什么 - 你不认为愿望能成真的…
- Now, just tell me what's going on. - You don't think that wishes can really?
什么？
What?
算了吧
Forget it.
算了吧 我只是
Forget it. I'm just, uh
很高兴见到你 就这些
I'm happy to see you, that's all.
你真漂亮
You're beautiful.
什么？
What?
我小时候
Hey, when I was, uh
这里有没有着过火？
When I was young, was there ever a fire here?
从来没有
No, never.
我以为发生过
I thought there was.
我猜我错了
I guess I was wrong.
爸爸在垒球队
Dad's on a softball team?
爸爸的垒球队
Dad's softball team. It's
对我来说很可笑
That's funny to me.
他热爱那个蠢队
He loved that stupid team.
爸爸过世了？
Dad's dead?
杀了他的是…
And the thing that killed him was a
中风啊
A stroke.
他死在睡梦中 你知道的
He died in his sleep, you know that.
- 太好了 - 你说什么？
- That's great. - Excuse me?
我说他死的很安祥
That's great. That he went peacefully, I mean, it-
这样对他很公平
It sure beats the alternative.
你喝多了吧？
You've been drinking.
我没有 妈妈
No, I haven't. Mom.
我打电话让卡门来接你好吗？
I'm just gonna call Carmen and have her come pick you up, okay?
等等 不不 别这么做
Wait. No. Don't do-Don't do that. Don't do that.
- 我想待在这儿 - 为什么？
- I wanna stay here. - Why?
因为我想念这个地方
Because I miss the place.
没关系的 你去睡吧
It's okay. You go to bed, okay?
你肯定你没事吗？
Are you sure you're all right?
我想是的
I think so.
好吧
Okay.
休息下吧
Get some rest.
我爱你
I love you.
我也是
Me too.
是我 我现在不能接电话
Hey, it's me. I can't come to the phone-
我不认为你是我班上的
Well, I don't think I've seen you in my class before.
没开玩笑吧？我很喜欢你的讲座
You kidding me? I love your lectures.
你让上学变的有趣
You make learning fun. Ha-ha.
那我能为你做什么？
So, what can I do for you?
跟我说说妖魔吧
What can you tell me about jinns?
很多穆斯林认为 妖魔是真实存在的
A lot of Muslims believe the jinn are very real.
- "古兰经"里写到过… - 实现愿望那部分
- They're mentioned in the Koran. - Yeah, I know. Get to the wish part.
- 那怎么了？- 他们真的能做到吗？
- What about it? - Do you think they could really do it?
不 我不认为他们能做到
Uh, no. No, I don't think they can really do it.
你明白它们是神话里的对吗？
You understand, these are mythic creatures.
是啊 我知道 我指在故事里…
Yeah. No, I know. I know. But, uh, I mean, in the stories.
比如说你有个愿望 但你从来没说出过口
You know, say you had a wish, uh, but you never even said it out loud.
像你
You know, like, that, uh...
爱的人从来都没死 那些糟糕的事从来 没发生过
That a loved one never died or that, uh, something awful never happened.
也许是这样
Supposedly, yes.
它们有神一般的力量 它们能随心所欲的改变现实…
I mean, they have godlike power. They can alter reality however they want.
过去 现在 未来
Past, present, future.
妖魔为什么要这么做？
Why would the jinn do it?
自卫吗？也许根本就不是魔鬼
What, self defense? Or maybe it's not really evil.
年轻人？
Son.
你喝多了吧？
You been drinking?
每个人都这么问我 但我没有
Everybody keeps asking me that, but, uh, no.
你以为你是谁？我们都是平民
Who'd have thought, baby? We're civilians.
嘿 你怎么了
Hey! What's the matter with you?
- 这是世界上最好吃的三明治 - 谢谢
- Mm. This is the best sandwich ever. - Thank you.
我在找萨姆 他在哪儿？
I tried to get ahold of Sam earlier. Where-? Where is he?
他不久就会来的
Oh, he'll be here soon.
我很想见他
Good. I'm dying to see him.
亲爱的 别想歪了
Sweetie, uh, don't get me wrong.
你在这里我感到很奇怪 这么突然
I'm thrilled you're hanging out here all of a sudden.
但你是不是应该去工作了？
But, uh, shouldn't you be at work?
工作？
Work?
在车库里？
At the garage.
当然 车库
Right. The garage.
那是我工作的地方 今天我休息
That's where I work. Yeah. No. I've got the day off. Ha.
真是件好事
Good thing.
草坪要锄草了
The lawn looks like it could use some mowing.
- 你想要锄草？- 开玩笑吧？我很乐意锄草
- You wanna mow the lawn? - You kidding me? I'd love to mow the lawn.
那就去吧
Knock yourself out.
你知道你一生中都没锄过草
Think you'd never mowed a lawn in your life.
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
杰西卡
Jessica. Ha.
很高兴见到你 迪恩
Good to see you too, Dean.
你把我压着了
Can't breathe.
萨姆 瞧瞧你
Sammy, look at you.
你和杰西卡 我真不敢相信
You're with Jessica. That's-I don't believe it.
是啊
Yeah.
你们从哪里来？
Where'd you guys come from?
- 刚从加州回来 - 加州
- We just flew in from California. - California.
斯坦福啊？一定是法律学院吧
Stanford, huh? Law school, I bet.
妈妈的生日派对 还没开始你就开动了
I see you started off Mom's birthday with a bang, as usual.
妈妈的生日派对 今天吗？
Wait, Mom's birthday? That's today?
是的 迪恩 就是今天 我们来着就是为了这个
Yeah. Yeah, Dean, that's today. That's why we're here.
别和我说你忘记了
Don't tell me you forgot.
这太棒了
Wow, that looks awesome.
好了
All right.
向我们的妈妈 生日快乐
To Mom. Happy birthday.
- 生日快乐 - 谢谢你们
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
为了妈妈 干杯
To Mom. Cheers.
昨晚我真为你担心
I was really worried about you last night.
我很好
Oh, I'm-I'm good.
我真的没事
I'm really good.
好吧
Okay.
等会儿给你弄个芝士汉堡怎么样？
What do you say later we get you a cheeseburger?
太好了
Oh, God, yes.
我怎么会泡上你的？
How did I end up with such a cool chick?
我的标准比较低嘛
I just got low standards.
好了 杰西和我还有一个惊喜
All right, Jess and I actually have another surprise for Mom's birthday.
- 你想告诉他们吗？- 他们是你的家人
- Uh, you wanna tell them? - They're your family.
- 好吧 - 是什么？告诉我是什么？
All right. - What? Tell me what?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
太好了 恭喜了 谢谢
That's wonderful. Congratulations. Thank you.
恭喜了 谢谢
Congratulations. Thank you.
我很兴奋
I'm so excited.
我真希望你爸爸也在场
I just wish your dad was here.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
给我看看那个戒指
Jessica, let me see that ring.
- 恭喜你 萨姆 - 谢谢
- Congratulations, Sammy. - Thanks.
我真的希望你幸福
I'm really glad you're happy.
那么 迪恩 餐厅里
So, Dean, what was, uh...?
你看到什么了？
What was all that back at the restaurant?
我想我看到一个人了 没事的
Oh, I thought I saw someone. I'm sure it's nothing.
这个生日我过的很开心 谢谢你们
Well, I had a lovely birthday. Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
- 晚安 妈妈 - 好了 我要走了
- Night, Mom. - Yeah, well, I'm beat.
- 你准备好了吗？- 当然
- Ready to turn in? - Sure.
- 大家晚安 - 晚安
- Good night, guys. Good night.
等等 等等 还没过9点呐
Wait a second. Wait a second. Come on, it's not even 9:00 yet.
我们一起喝一杯吧
Let's go have a drink or something.
- 下次吧 - 来吧 瞧瞧我们
- Maybe another time. - Come on, man. Look at us.
我们的女人多漂亮 你订婚了
Huh? We both have beautiful women on our arms. You're engaged.
我们一起来庆祝吧
Let's go celebrate.
失陪一下 我和我兄弟有话要说
Guys, can you excuse us? I just wanna talk to my brother.
- 当然 - 谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks.
来吧 卡门
Come on, Carmen.
我要问你…
So I needed to ask you...
这边来
Come here.
怎么了？
What?
好吧
Okay.
你中什么邪了？
What's gotten into you?
- 你指什么？- 我指这一切
- What do you mean? - I mean, this whole...
过度 热情的举止
warm, fuzzy Ecstasy-trip thing.
我为你感到高兴 萨姆
I'm just happy for you, Sammy.
这另当别论 你什么时候开始叫我萨姆的？
Yeah. Right. That's another thing. Since when do you call me "Sammy"?
拜托 迪恩 我们在假期外根本不说话
Dean. Come on. We don't talk outside of holidays.
不吗？
We don't?
我们应该谈谈 你是我兄弟啊
Well, we should. I mean, you're my brother. Ha.
"你是我兄弟"？是啊 你还偷走了我的信用卡
"You're my brother." You know, that's what you said when you snagged my ATM card.
还有你在我的毕业典礼 上被保释出来？你还骗走了瑞秋·内夫
Or when you bailed on my graduation. Or when you hooked up with Rachel Nave.
谁？
Who?
我的舞伴
Uh, my prom date.
在舞会上
On prom night.
那听起来真像我
Yeah, that does kind of sound like me.
- 我对这一切都感到很抱歉 - 没关系的 老兄
- Well, hey, man, I'm sorry about all that. - No. Look. It's all right, man. I just-
我没让你改变 我只是…
You know, I'm not asking you to change. I just, uh...
我不知道
I don't know.
我猜我们就是 没有什么共同点 你知道吗？
I guess we just don't really have anything in common. You know?
- 等等 我们有的 我们有啊 - 什么？
- Whoa, whoa. Yes, we do. Yes, we do. Ha. - What?
- 猎杀啊 - 打猎？
- Hunting. - Hunting?
我从来没打过猎 迪恩
I've never been hunting in my life, Dean.
我们应该抽空去玩玩
Yeah, well, we should go sometime.
你很擅长这个的
I think you'd be great at it.
去歇会儿吧
Get some rest.
我的最爱 你一定很了解我
My favorite. I guess you know me pretty well.
恐怕是这样
Afraid so.
你没事吧？
You all right?
萨姆和我总合不来
Sammy and I, we don't get along.
你们不经常在一起
Well, you don't really spend a lot of time together.
你们对对方不是很了解
I mean, I just think you don't know each other all that well.
他不知道自己失去的是什么
For the record, he doesn't know what he's missing.
我能补偿萨姆
I could fix things with Sam.
我能补偿他…
I can make it up to him.
为了大家
To everyone.
好吧
Okay.
最近你是怎么了？
What's gotten into you lately?
你绝对不会相信的
This isn't gonna make a lick of sense to you.
我感觉我有了第二次机会
But I kind of feel like I've been given a second chance.
我不想放弃它
And I don't wanna waste it.
是啊 确实没什么道理
You're right. That doesn't make any sense.
我知道了
You know, I get it.
知道什么了？
Get what?
为什么是你
Why you're the one.
不管你怎么了 但我很喜欢
Whatever's gotten into you, I like it.
拜托 别这样对我 我还要去上班呢
Oh, come on. Don't do this to me now. I've gotta get ready for work.
现在吗？
You gotta work now?
我告诉过你 周四我有夜班
I told you. I've got the night shifts on Thursday.
你在…
You work nights at the, uh...?
医院
Hospital.
我和一个护士在约会
I'm dating a nurse.
真是体面啊
That is so respectable.
橄榄油在这里一定有用处
The olive oil must have a purpose here.
我拿了橄榄油 我们就放
I'll take the olive oil, and we'll just put a-
一点橄榄油进去 就这样
Just a touch of olive oil in. Okay. That's all.
这个机器不会出差错的
You can't make any mistakes with this machine.
这些液体呢 可以用水
Now, for liquid, I could use water...
但我要用点…
but I'm gonna use a little spinach-
今天是联合航空公司
And today marks the anniversary of the crash...
坠毁的周年纪念日
of United Britannia Flight 424.
当地的居民手持蜡烛 在此守夜
Indianapolis residents held a candlelight vigil...
为了纪念108名死去的乘客 和机组人员
in memory of the passengers and crew...
- 不 不 我阻止了那次坠机 - 谁失去了生命
- No. No, I stopped that crash. - ...who lost their lives-
他们所有的人…
All of them.
每个你救的人 我和萨姆救的人…
Everyone that you saved. Everyone Sammy and I saved.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
还有一个女人一直在徘徊
And there's this woman haunting me.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
我不清楚这有什么联系 至少现在还不清楚
I don't know what the connection is. Not yet anyway.
就好像对那个世界 还念念不忘
It's like my old life is coming after me or something, you know?
就像它不想让我快乐
Like it doesn't want me to be happy.
当然我知道你要怎么说
Of course, I know what you'd say.
不是打垒球的那个人
Well, not the you that played softball, but...
你对我说"去猎杀那些妖魔" 它把你弄到这里 它也能把你弄回去
You'd say, "Go hunt the jinn. Hey, it put you here, it could put you back.
你的幸福还是所有这些人的生命？对吗？
Your happiness for all those people's lives. No contest, right?"
但为什么？
But why?
为什么是我要救他们
Why is it my job to save these people?
为什么我要当什么英雄？
Why do I have to be some kind of hero?
我们怎么办？
What about us, huh?
妈妈不应该还活着？萨姆不应该结婚？
What, Mom's not supposed to live her life? Sammy's not supposed to get married?
我们为什么要牺牲一切 爸爸？
Why do we have to sacrifice everything, Dad?
这…
It's-
是啊
Yeah.
太简单了 我为你而感到羞耻
That was so easy, I'm embarrassed for you.
迪恩？你在这儿干嘛？
Dean? What the hell are you doing here?
我在找酒喝
I was looking for a beer.
在放瓷器的柜子里找？
In the china cabinet?
- 那是妈妈的银器 - 萨姆
- That's Mom's silver. - Sam
干什么 你闯进来就是为了
What, you broke into the house...
- 偷妈妈的银器 - 不是你看到的那样 好吗？
- ...to steal Mom's silver? - It's not what it looks like.
- 我没得选择 哦 是吗 - 为什么？
- I didn't have a choice. - Oh, really? Why?
有什么是那么该死的重要 重要到你要去偷自己妈妈的银器？
What's so damn important that you gotta steal from your mother?
- 你想要知道真相吗 - 是的 是的 我想要知道
- You want the truth? - Yeah. Yeah, I do.
我欠人钱
I owe somebody money.
- 谁 - 一个赛马的赌注者 我输了很多
- Who? - A bookie. I lost big on a game.
- 我今天晚上就要带现金去给他 - 我不敢相信我们居然有血缘关系
- I gotta bring him the cash tonight. - I can't believe we're even related.
萨姆 对不起
Sam, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉我们相处得不太好
I'm sorry that we don't get along.
我真的希望可以留下来弥补这一切
And I wish to hell I could stay and fix it.
但是我一定要做这件事
But I gotta do this.
人们的生命就悬在这上面了
People's lives depend on it.
你在说什么呢 迪恩？
What are you talking about, Dean?
没什么 忘掉吧 只是 呃…
Nothing. Forget it. Just, uh...
嘿 告诉妈妈我爱她
Hey, tell Mom I love her.
迪恩
Dean.
再见 萨姆
I'll see you, Sammy.
- 下车 - 我要和你一起去
- Get out car. - I'm going with you.
- 你只会拖我后腿 - 这很危险
- You're gonna slow me down. - Tough.
- 你可能会受伤的 - 你也是啊
- You could get hurt. - And so could you.
- 萨姆 - 听着 无论你要做的是什么蠢事
- Sam...Whatever stupid thing you're about to do...
你不可能一个人去做 就这样
you're not doing it alone. And that's that.
我不明白 你为什么要这样？
I don't understand. Why are you doing this?
因为你终究还是我哥哥
Because you're still my brother.
贱人
Bitch.
你… 你叫我贱人做什么？
What are you calling me a bitch for?
- 你应该回敬我一句"混蛋"的 - 什么？
- You're supposed to say, "jerk." - What?
没关系了
Never mind.
- 包里面是什么 - 没什么
- What's in the bag? - Nothing.
- 没什么吗 - 是的 没什么
- Nothing? - Yeah, nothing.
很好
Fine.
- 你不会想要那么做的 - 哦 是吗？
- You don't wanna do that. - Oh, really?
- 该死的这是什么东西 - 血
- What the hell is this? - Blood.
是啊 我看得出来这是血来着 但是这东西在这是要干嘛？
Yeah, I can see that it's blood, Dean. What the hell is it doing in here?
- 你不会真想要知道的 - 不 我真的想要知道
- You don't really wanna know. - No, I do really wanna know.
- 我真的 真的想知道 - 好吧 反正你迟早都会知道的
- I really, really do. - Well, you're gonna find out sooner or later.
我需要一把沾着羊血的银刃
I needed a silver knife dipped in lamb's blood.
你需要一把沾着羊血的银刀 为什么？
You needed a silver knife dipped in lamb's blood why?
因为有这样一种生物 一个神灵 我要去猎捕它
Because there's this creature, a jinn, and I have to hunt it.
好吧 呃
Okay. Um...
- 停车 - 我知道这听起来很疯狂
- Stop the car. - I know how it sounds.
- 太好了 停车 - 这是真的 萨姆
- Great. Just stop the car. - It's the truth, Sam.
在外面的黑暗中真的有些东西存在着 那些邪恶的东西
There are things out in the dark. There are bad things.
那些像噩梦一般的东西
There are nightmare things.
人们需要被拯救 而如果我们不去救他们 就没人会了
People have to be saved. If we don't save them, then nobody will.
所以我只好… 我希望
So I just...I wish.
这是干什么 迪恩 那是我的电话
What the hell was that? That was my phone.
我不会呆到一间橡皮房去 萨姆 而且我们有工作要做
I'm not going to a rubber room. And we got work to do.
我只是试着要帮助你 迪恩
I was just trying to help.
- 我不想你把自己弄伤 - 你在保护我？
- I don't want you to get hurt. - What, you protect me?
- 是的 - 哦 那真值得高兴
- Yeah. - Oh, that's hilarious.
你为什么不坐坐好 然后试着别让我们两个都被杀掉？
Why don't you just sit tight and try not to get us both killed?
- 我们在哪 - 恩 我们已经不在堪萨斯州了
Where are we? - Well, we're not in Kansas anymore.
伊利诺斯州
Illinois.
你认为有东西在那里？
And you think something's in there?
我知道有
I know it is.
看到了吗 这里什么也没有 迪恩
See? There's nothing here, Dean.
听着 卡门会担心死你的 迪恩 来吧 我们走吧
Look, Carmen's gotta be worried sick about you, Dean. Come on, let's just go.
那该死的是什么东西？
What the hell is that?
呆在我后面别说话
Stay behind me. Keep your mouth shut.
该死的这是怎么了？
What the hell?
是她
It's her.
迪恩 发生了什么事？嘘
Dean, what's going on?
我的爸爸在哪儿？
Where's my dad?
我不知道 不
I don't know. No.
不 我爸在哪儿？
Don't. No. Where's my dad?
睡吧
Sleep.
- 这是真的吗 你没有疯 - 她不知道她在哪里
This is real? You're not crazy? - She didn't know where she was.
她以为她正和她父亲在一起
She thought she was with her father.
如果这就是神灵所做的怎么办？
What if that's what the jinn does?
它并没有实现你的愿望
It doesn't grant you a wish.
- 它只是让你以为愿望被实现了 - 听着 兄弟 那东西随时可能回来
- It just makes you think it has. - Look, man, that thing could come back...
好吗
all right?
迪恩
Dean.
拜托
Please.
如果我和她一样怎么办？
What if I'm like her?
如果我也被绑在这里的某一处怎么办？
What if I'm tied up in here someplace?
如果这一切都是我想象的怎么办？
What if all this is in my head?
我的意思是 这有可能的 你知道
I mean, it could, you know...
可能它给了我们某些超自然的幻觉
Maybe it gives us some kind of supernatural acid...
- 然后慢慢的喝我们的血 - 不 迪恩 那根本说不通 好吗？
- ...and then just feeds on us slow. - No. Dean, that doesn't make sense, okay?
如果这就是她一直出现在我面前的原因怎么办？
What if that's why she keeps appearing to me?
她不是鬼魂
She's not a spirit.
就好象我越来越能捕捉到现实中的片段
It's like more and more I'm catching flashes of reality. I'm in here somewhere.
我很紧张
I'm catatonic.
就好象我在这里的某处不停的接收这些幻想
And I'm taking all this stuff in.
却停不下来也醒不过来
But I can't snap out of it.
好了 听着 是的你是对的 我错了 你没疯
Yeah. Okay. Look, you're right. I was wrong. You're not crazy.
但是我们要快些离开这里
But we-We need to get out of here. Fast.
我不认为你是真的
I don't think you're real.
你感觉到了吗 你感觉到了吗 我是真实的 这不是一次迷幻之旅
Did you feel that? You feel this? I'm real. This is not an acid trip.
我是真的 然后那东西会回来这里把我们两个真的都杀掉
I'm real and that thing's gonna come down here and kill us for real.
- 现在 拜托 - 有一个办法去确定
- Now, please. - There's one way to be sure.
喂 喂 喂 喂
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
这是一个古老的传说 如果在梦里你就快要死掉了 你就会醒过来
It's an old-wives' tale. If you're about to die in a dream, you wake up.
- 不 不 不 那太疯狂了 好吗 - 也许
- No. No. No. That's crazy, all right? - Maybe.
- 你会杀了你自己 - 或者我会清醒过来
- You're gonna kill yourself-Okay. - Or I'm gonna wake up.
- 两者中的一个 - 听着
- One or the other. - Look.
这不是一场梦 好吗 我现在正和你在一起
This isn't a dream, all right? I'm here, with you, now...
而你就快要弄死自己了 迪恩
and you are about to kill yourself, Dean.
不 我挺有把握的…
No, I'm pretty sure.
大概90%肯定
Like 90 percent sure.
但是已经足够确定了
But I'm sure enough.
等等
Wait!
为什么你要不停的追究？
Why'd you have to keep digging?
为什么你就不能好好和我们在一起？
Why couldn't you have left well enough alone?
你是快乐的
You were happy.
把刀放下 亲爱的
Put the knife down, honey.
你不是真实的
You're not real.
所有的这一切都不是
None of it is.
并没有关系啊
It doesn't matter.
这仍然比你所拥有的东西都好
It's still better than anything you had.
- 什么 - 这是所有你想要的
- What? - It's everything you want.
我们又是一家人了
We're a family again.
回家吧
Let's go home.
我会死
I'll die.
那个神灵几天内就会把我喝干
The jinn'll drain the life out of me in a couple of days.
但是在这里 和我们在一起
But in here, with us, it'll feel like years...
好像一辈子
like a lifetime.
我保证
I promise.
不再有伤痛 不再有恐惧
No more pain or fear.
只有爱 舒适 和安稳
Just love and comfort and safety.
迪恩 和我们一起
Dean. Stay with us.
休息一下
Get some rest.
你不用再担心萨姆
You don't have to worry about Sam anymore.
你会看着他一辈子
You get to watch him live a full life.
我们会有个未来
We can have a future together.
组成我们自己的家庭
Have our own family.
我爱你 迪恩
I love you, Dean.
求你
Please.
为什么拯救所有人是我们的责任？
Why is it our job to save everyone?
我们做得还不够么？
Haven't we done enough?
我在乞求你
I'm begging you.
给我那把刀
Give me the knife.
对不起
I'm sorry.
迪恩
Dean!
Dean.
迪恩
哦 上帝
Oh, God. Come on.
嘿 醒一醒
Hey, wake up.
醒醒 该死的
Wake up, damn it.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
嗨 是你
Oh, Auntie Em.
这世上就没地方会像家一样了
There's no place like home.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
- 有一瞬间我以为我失去你了 - 你差一点点就失去我了
- I thought I lost you for a second. - You almost did.
让我把你放下来
Let's get you down.
萨姆
Sam!
快啊
Come on!
她还活着 萨姆
She's still alive. Sam.
我找到你了
I got you.
我找到你了 我们把你从这里弄出去 好吗？
I got you. We're gonna get you out of here, okay?
我找到你了
I got you.
好的 呃 好吧 非常感谢你提供的信息 好吧 再见
Okay. Uh, thank you so much for the update. Okay. Bye.
是医院 那个女孩的状况已经稳定下来了
That was the hospital. The girl's been stabilized.
好运气 她会熬过去的
Good chance she's gonna pull through.
- 那很好 - 是啊
- That's good. - Yeah.
你呢 你还好吗
How about you? You all right?
是的 我还好
Ahem. Yeah, I'm all right.
你该看看的 萨姆
You should've seen it, Sam.
我们的生活
Our lives.
你是个那样的好人
You were such a wussy.
所以 我们不太合得来了 对吧？
So we didn't get along, then, huh?
- 不 - 是啊
- No. - Yeah.
我以为应该是那种完美幻想
I thought it was supposed to be this perfect fantasy.
不是
It wasn't.
那只是一个愿望
It was just a wish.
我希望妈妈活着
Yeah, I wished for Mom to live.
妈妈一直没死 我们也一直没有去猎魔 然后你和我也一直没有
If Mom never died, we never went hunting. And you and me just never, uh...
- 你知道的 - 是的
- ...you know. - Yeah.
我很高兴我们能像现在这样
Well, I'm glad we do.
然后我也很高兴你把你自己拉出来了
And I'm glad you dug yourself out, Dean.
大部分人不会有这种力量 他们会选择留下
Most people wouldn't have had the strength. They would have stayed.
是啊 幸运的我
Yeah. Lucky me.
我该告诉你的 尽管 你有了杰西
I gotta tell you, though, man. You had Jess.
妈妈就快要有孙子孙女了
Mom was gonna have grandkids.
是的 但是 迪恩 那不是真的
Yeah, but, Dean, it wasn't real.
我知道
I know.
但我想留下
But I wanted to stay.
我那么那么的想要留下
I wanted to stay so bad.
我的意思是 自从爸爸死了之后…
I mean, ever since Dad...
我所能想到的都是这份工作让我们付出了怎样的代价
all I can think about is how much this job's cost us.
我们失去了太多
We've lost so much.
我们也
We've...
牺牲了太多
sacrificed so much
但是人们因为你而得救活了下来 都值得 迪恩 值得了
But people are alive because of you. It's worth it, Dean.
这不公平
It is. It's not fair.
你知道的 这真的很伤 但是它值得
And, you know, it hurts like hell, but it's worth it.